http://www.peru.edu/privacypolicy

Student Records
Need Academic Assistance?
Alerts
Sign Up Now!
Stay up to date on school closings and other important alerts.
Schedule a Visit
Why Peru State?
Cost & Aid
Earn a scholarship just for coming to campus and taking a selfie. Learn more now!
TRiO | Student Success Services
Peru State's award-winning education isn't just available in the classroom. Many of our programs are also offered online.
Current Students & Faculty
Peru State's online programs give you the flexibility to complete your degree on your time. They are also recognized nationally for affordability.
College Catalog
Peru State's Graduate degree programs are offered entirely online. These programs are flexible enough to fit your schedule. Learn more now!
Peru State Times
Peru State offers more than a great education. With a variety of clubs and activities, you're sure to find something you love at Peru State. Learn more now!
Athletics
Menu
Request Info
Apply
Visit
AboutPrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
About Home
Privacy Policy
Peru State College takes privacy seriously and requests only the personal identifiable information (PII) needed to conduct the business of the college. This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for https://www.peru.edu. By using this website, you consent to our collection and use of information in accordance with this privacy policy.
Information Collected
Peru State collects, stores and uses the following types of personal information:
Cookies
Cookies are small files that are stored on your computer (unless you block them). We use cookies to understand and save your preferences and may compile aggregate data about site traffic and interaction for the purpose of improving the user experience.
Personal Identifiable Information (PII)
We collect PII from you for the sole purpose of providing the services you request. The types of information requested may include: email addresses, name, address, phone numbers and academic background. When providing information other than your own PII (information about a third party), you certify that you have permission to share such information, and that this privacy policy has been shared with the applicable third party.
University of Nebraska Supported Systems
Peru State College is closely affiliated with the University of Nebraska for the student information system and financial and human resource systems. You consent to the University of Nebraska policies when accessing these systems.
Partners and Service Providers
When appropriate, the College may use service providers to collect data for services including, but not limited to, services associated with athletics, college transfers, scholarships, assessment, information security training, email, and payment card processing. While Peru State uses care in selecting service providers, we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of service provider websites. We encourage users to be cautious when leaving our website and to evaluate third party privacy policies. Some of these service providers have access to personal data about you that Peru State may not otherwise have, and the service providers may share some or all of this personal data with us as needed to provide you with the services you request.
Collected Information Use
We will not share, sell or authorize any third party to use the information that you provided without your permission unless required by law. The information that you provide is used to deliver the services necessary to conduct college business. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary. We also use the email addresses and phone numbers that you provide for sending you public information about the College. We may also provide your information to third parties in circumstances where we believe that doing so is necessary or appropriate to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request. The information may also be used to detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues and to protect the rights and safety of others.
Information Protection
Peru State uses reasonable security measures to help protect the information within our control from loss, misuse, and alteration. Peru State complies with applicable state and federal privacy statutes including the Higher Education Opportunity Act (HEOA), Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA), the Nebraska Public Records Law, and Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act (GLBA). Only college representatives who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information (PII). The computer system used to store PII are contained within a secure environment. While reasonable security and compliance measures are used, we recognize that no method of internet data transmission and electronic data storage is completely secure.
Data Correction, Review, Retention and Contacting Peru State
Peru State will retain information about you as needed for the purposes set out in this policy unless a longer period is required under applicable law or as otherwise required to comply with legal obligations. You can request to review and revise the information that Peru State has maintained about you by submitting the associated revision form on this website, or by contacting the Peru State Registrar listed within this website.  If you need to contact Peru State for reasons other than to update information that Peru State maintains about you, please visit the contact page on our website.
Policy Revisions
This privacy policy may be amended at Peru State’s discretion with changes posted at this webpage.
Explore Campus
Request Info
Visit
Apply
Student Portal
Faculty & Staff
Foundation
Parents | Visitors
Schedule a Visit
Why Peru State?
Directions to Campus
Campus Map
Request More Information
Transfer to Peru State
Programs | Majors
Cost & Aid
Earn a scholarship just for coming to campus and taking a selfie. Learn more now!
Academics
School of Arts & Sciences
School of Education
School of Professional Studies
Graduate Programs
All Programs/Majors
Apply for Admission
Bookstore
TRiO | Student Success Services
Peru State's award-winning education isn't just available in the classroom. Many of our programs are also offered online.
Online Programs
Apply for Admission
High School Dual Enrollment
Undergraduate
Graduate
Tuition & Costs
Accreditation
Prior Learning Life Experience
Ask an Advisor
Request More Information
Blackboard
Search for Classes
Current Students & Faculty
Peru State's online programs give you the flexibility to complete your degree on your time. They are also recognized nationally for affordability.
Graduate Degrees
Master of Education
Master of Organizational Management
Apply for Admission
Tuition and Costs
Request More Information
Admissions
Accreditation
College Catalog
Peru State's Graduate degree programs are offered entirely online. These programs are flexible enough to fit your schedule. Learn more now!
Student Life
Residence Life
Residence Halls
How to Apply for Housing
Student Handbook
Student Activities
Forms Bank
Student Senate
First Year Experience
Dining Services
Campus Safety
Title IX Information
Peru State Times
Peru State offers more than a great education. With a variety of clubs and activities, you're sure to find something you love at Peru State. Learn more now!
Athletics
Students
Popular Resources
Blackboard
Bookstore
Financial Aid
Bobcat 360 Login
myPSC
Need Academic Assistance?
Sign Up Now!
Stay up to date on school closings and other important alerts.
